

Github: www.github.com/anniezhou301
Online Portfolio: anniezhou301.github.io
Linkedin: www.linkedin.com/in/anniezhou301

Email: azhou@ucvts.tec.nj.us

SKILLS

Proficient:

Familiar:

-HTML/CSS -Python
-Javascript -MongoDB

-JQuery -node.js/Express.js

-Java -Jade

-Git -Angular.js

OBJECTIVE

I'm a junior in high school passionate about programming and math, and would love an opportunity to get my hands dirty in the field. As you can see by the extracurriculars I do in high school as well as the programming experience I gained outside of school, I'm driven and eagar to learn.

EXPERIENCE

Director of Technology

HackUC| 2015-Present

Board of Founders (2015)

Created the official website - www.hackuc.com - from scratch (including logo) and organized and mentored at the event. Led the development of the 2015-16 official website, working on UI/UX, interactivity, SEO, and speed optimization. It was created using HTML/CSS/Javascript, and has a node.js backend. Created sponsorship package and worked on cold-emailing potential companies and communicating with them.

 ${\sf Gained\ expertise\ in:\ HTML/CSS,\ JavaScript,\ Node.js,\ MongoDB}$

EDUCATION

Introduction to Programming

Union County Magnet High School

Object-oriented programming course based in Processing.js, a library of Java. Created Doodle Jump Clone, Pong game, Raindrop Catching Game, Physics-Based Calculator.

Took AP Computer Science in 2015, recieved 5 (out of 5)

Free Code Camp Front End Cerification

Gained proficiency in: APIs, Javascript, Node.js, MongoDB, Algorithms.

Created Simon Game, Tic Tac Toe Al, Wikipedia Viewer, and many more projects.

AWARDS

NCWIT Aspirations Award National Runner Up

National Center for Women in Technology - Awarded to 1% of applicants in the nation

Google Code In

Participant and T-shirt winner.

Contributed to open source code - Fossasia and MetaBrainz
Learned React, Node.js

Science Olympiad

Captain(2016)

States 1st Place:

Designer Genes(2015)

Invitationals 1st Place

Protein Modeling(2016)

OTHER RELEVANT COURSES

Linear Algebra (2016)

Multivariable Calculus (2015-16)

AP Physics Electricity and Magnetism C (2015-16)

Advanced Manufacturing and Project Management (2016)